Guide to the Cornell University Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries' administrative records, 1961-2003.
Cornell University Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries' administrative records, 1961-2003
- Series VI: Collections
  - 12T. Special Collections
    - 12.T.30 Maeda Collection, 1996-2000, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 12.T.40 Tibetan Collection (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - 12.V.10 Collection Develop. (Uris) - General (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 12.V.15 Library of Natural Sounds (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 12.V.40 Uris Science Withdrawal, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 12.V.45 Uris User Survey (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Series VII: Conservation
  - 14C. Conservation -General - CUL
    - 14.C.5 Conservation Funding, 1984-86, 1990-91 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 14.C.10 Conservation Officer, 1982-83, 1984-85 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - 14.C.15 Cornell Survey, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - 14.C.20 Manuals, 1980, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - 14.C.25 RLG--Preservation, 1981-83, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - 14.C.30 Preservation Program, 1939-1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - 14.C.35 Publicity, 1992-1995, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - 14.C.40 Southeast Asia Center--Proposed, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - 14.C.45 Staff and Space Needs, 1985-87 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - 14.C.50 Xerox Project, 1990, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 14E. Conservation - General - OKU
    - 14.E.5 Condition Surveys, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - 14.E.8 Insect Study, 1998, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - 14.E.10 Manuals, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - 14.E.15 Microformat Equipment-- Maintenance, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - 14.E.17 Newspaper Filming, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - 14.E.20 Olin Stack Furbishing Proj., 1983 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - 14.E.25 Xerox Preservation Project, 1990-91 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 14G. Conservation - Procedures - CUL
    - 14.G.5 Architectural Guidelines, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - 14.G.10 Binding and Book marking, 1982-85, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - 14.G.15 Book Repair, 1983-84 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - 14.G.20 Environmental Monitoring, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - 14.G.25 Fumigation, 1973-1983 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - 14.G.30 Preservation Microfilming, 1983-84, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - 14.G.35 Preservation Photocopying, 1983, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 14J. Conservation Committee
    - 14.J.5 Conservation Committee--General, 1983-84, 1986-88 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - 14.J.10 Conservation Committee--Minutes, 1980-88 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - 14.J.20 Policy and Planning Committee, 1992-93 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Series VIII: Correspondence
  - 16.C. Corson
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - 16.C.10 Corson Corresp. --General, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - 16G. General
    - 16.G.5 Appreciation, 84-85, 87, 89-90, 1992-2001 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - 16.G.10 Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - 16.G.15 Permissions, Publications, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Series IX. Departmental Administration
  - 18A. Access Services Dept.
    - 18.A.5 Access--Administration--Circ, 1981-2001 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 18.A.10 Access--Administration--ILS, 1981-2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 18.A.25 Access--Contracts & Charges--ILS, 1981-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 18.A.30 Access--Facilities, 1983, 1985-1988, 2000-99 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 18.A.40 Access--Personnel, 1983-1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 18C. Asia- General
    - 18.C.5 Asia--Administration, 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 18.C.20 Asia--Collection Development, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 18.C.30 Asia--Facilities, 1992-1993, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 18.C.40 Asia--Personnel, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 18.C.50 Asia/CTS Staff Transfer, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 18D. Collection Development
    - 18.D.5 Collection Development--Administration, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 18.D.20 Coll Dev.--Collection Development, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 18.D.30 Coll. Dev.--Facilities, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 18.D.40 Coll. Dev.--Personnel, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 18E. Echols Collection
    - 18.E.5 Echols-- Admin. General, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 18.E.5 Echols--Administration, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 18.E.5 Echols-Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - 18.E.5 Echols--Admin. General, 1984-89 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 18.E.5 Echols--Admin. General, 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - 18.E.5 Administration, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - 18.E.20 Echols--Collection Development, 1984-1994, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 18.E.30 Echols--Facilities, 1981-2000 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 18.E.40 Echols--Personnel, 1980-2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 18G. History of Science Collection
    - 18.G.5 Hist Sci--Administration, 1984, 1986-1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - 18.G.20 Hist Sci--Collection Development, 1986-87, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - 18.G.30 Hist Sci--Facilities, 1981-83, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - 18.G.40 Hist Sci--Personnel, 1979-1991 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 18J. Icelandic Collection
    - 18.J.5 Icelandic--Admin.--Gen, 1984-89 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - 18.J.10 Icelandic--Admin.Gen, 1990-94 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - 18.J.15 Icelandic--Admin.--Gen, 1995- (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - 18.J.20 Icelandic--Collection Development, 1982-1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - 18.J.30 Icelandic--Facilities, 1984-1992 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - 18.J.40 Icelandic--Personnel, 1984-85, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - 18.J.50 Icelandic--Islandica--General, 1984-87, 1990-89, 1994-98 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - 18.J.60 Icelandic--Visiting Curator, 1984-1992 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - 18L. Manuscripts and Archives
    - 18.L.5 M & A-- Administration, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - 18.L.20 M & A --Collection Development, 1981, 1984-1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 18.L.30 M & A --Facilities, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 18.L.40 M& A --Personnel, 1983-85, 1987-93 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 18N. Maps, Microtexts and Newspapers
    - 18.N.5 MMN--Administration, 1983-85, 1987, 1989-90 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 18.N.20 MMN --Collection Development, 1988, 90 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 18.N.30 MMN--Facilities, 1983, 1985-86, 1989-92 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 18.N.40 MMN--Personnel, 1986-87, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 18P. New York Historical Resources Center
    - 18.P.5 NYHRC --Administration, 1984-85, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 18.P.15 NYHRC--Advisory Group, 1978, 1983-84, 1986-87, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 18.P.20 NYHRC--Collection Development (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 18.P.30 NYHRC--Facilities (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 18.P.40 NYHRC--Personnel, 1984, 1986, 1989-90 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 18R. Rare Books Dept.
    - 18.R.5 Rare--Administration, 1984-1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - 18.R.20 Rare--Collection Development, 1979, 1980, 1982, 1984-1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - 18.R.30 Rare--Facilities, 1984, 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 18.R.40 Rare--Personnel, 1985-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 18T. Reference Dept.
    - 18.T.5 Reference--Administration, 1981-1987, 1991-2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - 18.T.20 Reference--Collection Development, 1985, 1987, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - 18.T.30 Reference--Facilities, 1985-86, 1989-92 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - 18.T.40 Reference--Personnel, 1983-89, 1990, 1992-97, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 18V. South Asia Collection
    - 18.V.5 South Asia--Administration, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - 18.V.5 South Asia Administration, 1992-1997 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - 18.V.20 South Asia--Collection Development, 1990-1998, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - 18.V.30 South Asia--Facilities, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - 18.V.40 South Asia--Personnel, 1992-94, 1996-98, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 18X. Wason Collection
    - 18.X.5 Wason Administration, 1980-81 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - 18.X.5 Wason--Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - 18.X.5 Wason--Administration, 1984-89 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - 18.X.5 Wason--Administration, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - 18.X.5 Wason--Administration, 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - 18.X.20 Wason--Collection Development, 1977, 1980-81, 1985-90, 92-94, 96-98 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - 18.X.30 Wason--Facilities, 1979-1998 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - 18.X.40 Wason--Personnel, 1984-1998 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Series X. Development and Public Affairs
  - 20B. External Funding - Cornell Sources
    - 20.B.5 East Asia Program--Support, 1988-2002 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - 20.B.20 Robison Fund--Financial Reports, 1974-2000 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - 20.B.22 Robison Fund--Library Projects, 1995-2000 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - 20.B.Robison Fund--Robison Committee, 1993-2001 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - 20.B.30 South Asia Program--Support, 1986-97, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - 20.B.35 Southeast Asia Program--Support, 1980-82, 1984-88, 1990, 1992-2000 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - 20C. External Funding - General
    - 20.C.5 Application Procedures, 1985, 1988-89, 1991, 1998-99 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 20.C.10 Federal Funding--General, 1976, 1979-80, 1986-87, 1994-95 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 20.C.11 Internal Grants Programs--CUL, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 20.C.12 International Funding--General, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 20.C.14 National Resource Centers, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 20.C.15 NEH Grants--General, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 20.C.20 Overhead Rates, 1977, 1985-90, 1992-97 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 20.C.25 Title II-C Grants--General, 1985-86, 1988, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 20.C.30 Title II-D Grants--General, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 20D. External Funding - Outside Sources
    - 20.D.2 Omnibus Bill- NYS, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 20.D.4 Gladys Brooks Foundation, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 20.D.6 NEH Challenge Grant, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 20.D.8 Dante Project--NEH, 1986-88 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 20.D.10 Echols II-C Application, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 20.D.12 Gannett Foundation, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 20.D.14 Archives Intern-NHPRC, 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 20.D.16 Echols Luce Application, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 20.D.18 Manuscript Conversion--RLF/AMC, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 20.D.20 RLG Great Collections Microfilming, 1988-91 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - 20.D.22 UMI Echols Microfilming, 1988- (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - 20.D.24 Echols Luce Grant, 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - 20.D.26 NEH Challenge Grant Appl., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - 20.D.28 Lindseth--French Rev., 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - 20.D.30 French Rev.--Title IIC Appl., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - 20.D.32 NEH Grant--Asia Recon, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - 20.D.34 NEH Grant (1991)--Severinghaus, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - 20.D.36 NEH Challenge Grant--, 1991-94 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - 20.D.38 Mae Fah Luang--Echols, 1995-97 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - 20.D.40 NCC Japanese Resources, 1996- (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - 20.D.42 Cambodian Microfilm Project, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - 20.D.46 freeman Foundation--Wason, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 20E. Fund Raising
    - 20.E.2 Atlantic Philanthropic Service Co., 1997, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - 20.E.5 Capital Campaign, 1990-95 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - 20.E.8 Challenge II Endowments--OKU, 1996-99 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - 20.E.10 Class of 1938, 1991-93 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - 20.E.12 Class of 1944, 1998-99 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - 20.E.15 Development--General--Olin, 1990, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - 20.E.18 Echols Collection--Fund Raising, 1993, 1995-96 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - 20.E.20 Electronic Classroom--Uris, 1993-95 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - 20.E.25 Kroch Fund Raising--General, 1989, 1991, 1994-95 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - 20.E.30 Library Associates, 1980-84, 1993, 1995, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - 20.E.35 Library Development--General, 1979-81, 1983-85, 1987, 1993-97 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - 20.E.40 New Endowments, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - 20.E.42 OKU Gifts Received, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - 20.E.43 Priorities, CUL, 1997-98, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - 20.E.44 University Priorities, 1996-99 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - 20.E.45 South Asia Collections--Fund Raising, 1991, 1994-95 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - 20.E.48 Stern Curatorship, 1995, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - 20.E.50 Student Employment Endowments, 1994-97, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - 20.E.55 Uris Fund Raising & Development, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - 20.E.55 Uris Fund Raising & Development, 1891-1992 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - 20.E.60 Wason Collection--Fund Raising, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - 20F. Gifts - Policies and Procedures
    - 20.F.5 Appraisals, 1974, 1976-77, 1981, 1983-85 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - 20.F.10 Gifts--General, 1979-1982, 1989, 1995-96 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - 20.F.15 Gifts and Exchange Unit, 1979-82, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - 20.F.20 Gifts Policy--CUL, 1980, 1994-96 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - 20G. Library Visits
    - 20.G.2 Campus Visit--Class of '63, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - 20.G.4 Campus visit--Library, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - 20.G.5 Campus Visit--Library, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - 20.G.8 Campus Visit--Library, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - 20.G.10 Library Visits--General, 1991-93 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - 20.G.10 Library Visits--General, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - 20.G.10 Library Visits--General, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 20.G.10 Library Visits--General, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 20.G.10 Library Visits--General, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 20.G.10 Library Visits--General, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 20.G.10 Library Visits--General, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 20.G.10 Library Visits--General, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 20.G.10 Library Visits--General, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 20.G.30 TECRO (Taiwan) Visit, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 20.G.31 Pramoeyda Visit, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 20.G.32 Danang University Visit, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 20.G.35 Tishman Visit, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 20.G.37 Lee, Teng-hui Visit, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 20H. Names Spaces
    - 20.H.5 Class of '57 Reading Room--Uris, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - 20.H.10 McCarthy Room--Olin, 1991, 1993-94 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - 20.H.20 Rawson Room--Kroch, 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - 20.H.25 Space Naming--Policies, 1985, 1989, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 20J. Presidential Councilors
    - 20.J.5 Councilors Visit, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - 20.J.10 Councilors Visit, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 20K. Public Affairs - General
    - 20.K.10 International Reception, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - 20.K.15 Mission Statements--CUL, 1986, 1988, 1991, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - 20.K.30 Organization and Staff, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - 20.K.35 Public Affairs Activities--Misc., 1993, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - 20.K.40 Student Employee Endowments, 1993-95 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 20L. Public Affairs - Individuals
    - 20.L.5 Hu, Tsu-Wang, 1996-97 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - 20.L.10 Kroch, Carl A., 1994, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - 20.L.15 Miller, Robert, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - 20.L.20 Siew, Nim Chee, 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 20M. Public Relations - General
    - 20.M.3 Cornell Emerituss Faculty, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - 20.M.5 Descriptions--Kroch, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - 20.M.10 Descriptions--Olin (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - 20.M.15 Descriptions--Uris (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - 20.M.20 Exhibits--Olin, 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - 20.M.22 Exhibits--RMC, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - 20.M.25 Faculty Relations, 1981, 1983, 1986, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - 20.M.26 Filing In Libraries, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - 20.M.27 Institutional Identity Project, 1996-97 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - 20.M.30.1 Newspaper Clippings--Miscellaneous 1 of 6, 1990, 1992-97, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 20.M.30.2 Newspaper Clippings--Library Hours 2 of 6, 1982, 1993, 1995, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 20.M.30.3 Newspaper Clippings--Circulation/Access Serv., 1990, 1993-94 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 20.M.30.4 Newspaper Clippings--Collections 4 of 6, 1990-95 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - 20.M.30.5 Newspaper Clippings--Budget Cuts 5 of 6, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - 20.M.30.6 Newspaper Clippings--Construction, 1993, 1997-98 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - 20.M.34 Press Relations, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - 20.M.35 Publicity--Olin, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - 20.M.45 Student Relations, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - 20N. Reunion
    - 20.N.5 President's Reception, 1983-89 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - 20.N.10 Reception--General, 1991-92 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (pre-1993), 1986-88, 1991-93 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (1993), 1993-94 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (1994), 1993-94 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (1995), 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (1996), 1995-96 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (1997), 1996-97 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (1998), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (1999), 1999 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (2000), 2000 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - 20.N.15 Reunion Activities (2001), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - 20P. Trustee/Council Weekend
    - 20.P.10 Council Weekend (pre-1995), 1987-88, 1990, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - 20.P.10 Council Weekend (1995), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - 20.P.10 Council Weekend (1996), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - 20.P.10 Council Weekend (1997), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - 20.P.10 Council Weekend (2000) (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - 20.P.10 Council Weekend (2001), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Series XI: Finances and Accounting
  - 22N. Budget - OKU Operating
    - 22.K Reduction Planning, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 22.K Reduction Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 22.K Reduction Planning, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 22.K Reduction Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - 22.K Reduction Planning, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - 22.N.5 Asia Collections Funding, 1994-2002 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - 22R. Faculty Budget Analysis (1993-95)
    - 22.R.10 Budget Analysis Report--Drafts (1994-95), 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - 22.R.20 Budget Analysis Report--Final (1995), 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - 22.R.30 CUL Data--Background, 1987-95 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - 22.R.40 Materials Budget Analysis (1993), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Series XII: Libraries (CUL) - General
  - 24A. Annex Library
    - 24.A.5 Collection Management, 1978-81, 1984, 1986-89, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - 24.A.10 Environment and Security, 1984, 1987-88, 1990, 1994-95, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - 24.A.15 General Information, 1984, 1987-1990, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - 24.A.30 Publicity-Expansion (1997/98), 1995-97 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - 24C. Cornell Libraries - General
    - 24.C.5 Administrative Staff--Former - includes photograph of Uris Library Staff 1987, 1990, 1994-96, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - 24.C.25 History--General, 1990, 1992, 1998, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - 24.C.35 Issues and Perspectives, 1986-87, 1995-96, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - 24.C.45 Miscellaneous, 1995-96 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - 24.C.50 Organization--CUL, 1983-85, 1988-89, 1992, 1994, 1996-99, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - 24E. Kroch Library - General
    - 24.E.3 Architectural Awards, 1992, 1994, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - 24.E.10 Atlantic Philanthropic Co., 1994-95, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - 24.E.15 Dedication, 1991-92 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - 24.E.19 Floor Plans, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - 24.E.20 General Information, 1992-93, 1996, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - 24.E.25 Informational Brochure, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - 24.E.35 Named Spaces (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - 24.e.5 Art Work, 1992-93, 1996, 1998-99 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - 24.E.45 Publicity, 1990-91, 1993, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - 24.E.50 Site Visits (By Others), 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - 24G. Olin Library - General
    - 24.G.5 Art Work, 1962, 1984-85, 1991-92, 1994, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - 24.G.10 Collection Size, 1986, 1988-91 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - 24.G.15 Current Periodicals Room, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - 24.G.18 Exhibit Cases (Olin), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - 24.G.20 Floor Plans (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - 24.G.25 General Information, 1977, 1988-89, 1993-94 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - 24.G.28 Named Spaces (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - 24.G.30 Organization--General, 1983-84, 1988-89 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - 24.G.32 Organization--Ref. Dept. (1992-94), 1991-92, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - 24.G.35 Patron Handbook, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - 24.G.40 Pest Control, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - 24.G.45 Union Card Catalog, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - 24J. Olin Library - History
    - 24.J.5 Construction, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - 24.J.10 General Historical Information, 1959, 1961-62, 1982, 1987-89, 1991, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - 24.J.15 Opening, 1961-62 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - 24.J.20 Pre-Olin Planning, 1082, 1955, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - 24L. Uris Library - General
    - 24.L.8 Cornell (Ezra) Portrait, 1884, 1898 1953, 1925, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 24.L.10 Donor Overlook, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 24.L.15 Exhibit Cases, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 24.L.20 Furnishings, 1963, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 24.L.25 Kirby Room, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 24.L.30 McGraw Tower, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 24.L.35 Named Spaces, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 24.L.37 Organization--[Uris Library], 1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 24.L.40 Uris Inventory, 1992-93 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 24.L.45 White Library Carpet Project (1990-91), 1990-91, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 24N. Uris Library - History
    - 24.N.5 Alumni News Articles, 1963, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - 24.N.10 Building Maintenance (1990-91), 1990-91 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 24.N.15 Building Maintenance (1991-92), 1991-93 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 24.N.30 Reorganization (1993), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 24.N.40 Tower Room, 1977-78, 1982-84, 1987-88, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Series XIII: Patron Services
  - 26A. Access/Circulation Policies
    - 26.A.5 Access Policies--General, 1988-92 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - 26.A.10 Circulation Policies, 1988-90, 1992, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - 26.A.15 Missing Book Procedures, 1983, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 26D. Faculty Studies - General
    - 26.D.10 Policies and Procedures, 1984, 1986, 1990, 1992- 1993, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 22A)
  - 26G. Graduate Studies
    - 26.G.10 Graduate Carrels, 1983, 1985-86, 1989, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - 26.G.20 Graduate Study Rooms--Gen., 1987, 1989, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - 26.G.30 Graduate Study Rooms--Reorganization (1989), 1988-89 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - 26J. Handicapped Services
    - 26.J.10 Americans w/ Disabilities Act, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - 26.J.20 Handicapped Access--General, 1978, 1982-83, 1987, 1992-93 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 26L. ILL Services
    - 26.L.40 ILL--General Policies, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - 26N. Patron Services -General
    - 26.N.2 Alumni Services, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)